ヒトデ？
そうけ…
焼いてみるの！
何か質問のある人ー
じゃあ今日はここまで！
わ～ 大き～い！
焼いてありゃ 何でも食べそうだよな
そうじゃな！ そいじゃあ とりあえず
ステラだめ！ それ胴体ついてるから！
さあ… 俺は食べた事ないな
シスターに 食わして
やりたいんじゃけど…
先生 ヒトデって食べられるんかのう？
あっははっ あの人なら
食えるんじゃない？
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかし VIPなエア・フォース
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの
どうして？ 知らない間に
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
M
L
N
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
M
L
N
Even still, though nowadays revenue
from BDs and DVDs is necessary to balance the
production budget, I continue to assume that they will not sell.
That's all for today. Any questions?
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
Teacher! Are starfish edible?
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
Starfish? I'm not sure. I've never tried before.
I was thinking of cooking one for Sister...
I'm sure he can stomach it. He'll try
anything if you cook it long enough.
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでも
そうなの？ いまなら間に合う
Yeah, I bet you're right!
Then let's get to grilling!
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
Man, that one's huge!
Stop, Stella! That one's got a body!
Chapter 70: "A Present"
She loves me, she loves me not, sh-sh-sh-sh—
スキ キライ スキ キライ…
う… うわ… この服のコーディネイト…
Whoa... his clothes.
He was wearing the same thing when he
ran off after seeing Nino and me kiss!
俺とニノさんがキスするのを見て
無言で出て行った時のと同じ…
Has he been like this ever since?
あれからずっと こうなのか！？
お おい 星っ！
Hey, Hoshi!
Starfish. I'm a starfish.
ヒトデです… 僕はヒトデ…
See? Starfish!
ホラ ヒトデじゃろ！
Get a grip, Hoshi!
しっかりしろよ 星！
I apologize for the confusion... but I'm
just a stinking, insignificant little—
いっけん星のような
紛らわしい姿ですみません…
けど僕は ちっぽけで潮臭いただの…
Hoshi!
星っ！
I'm a potato.
じゃがいもです…
Either way, he's lunch!
何にせよ 食材じゃな！
This one's gone bad.
どっちにしろ 腐っとる！
Yay, this'll be perfect!
よしっ 腕がなるわい！
Rec, you're my taste-tester!
リク わりゃあ味見係じゃ！
No way! He's all rotten!
嫌だよ！ 毒見じゃないか！
And why are you suddenly cooking for Sister?
大体何で急に シスターに料理なんか…
If you must know, it's to thank him!
へへーん 教えたるわ
これはな お礼なんじゃ
Thank him?
お礼？
Sister gave me a bra I've had my eye on forever!
シスターが わしが前から欲しがっとった
ブラジャーを買うてくれたんじゃ！
Bra?
ブラッ…！？
I guess Sister sees me as
a full-grown woman now.
シスターもきっと わしをもう大人じゃって
認めてくれたんじゃなあ！
He might even finally be in love with me!
もしかしたら わしの事
好きなのかもしれん…！
え… そんな… だってシスターは…
Huh? But Sister's set on...
Here, Rec!
ホレ リク！
You can look, just this once.
特別に見せたるわ！
Nice, huh?
似合っとるじゃろ？
Now I can take on bad guys all
by myself. I'm all grown up!
えへへ これでもう一人でも
敵陣に乗り込める 大人の女じゃ！
True... it's very well-designed.
うん… 素敵なデザインだね…
Bra-for-a-la-dy!
おっとな～の～…
It was a bulletproof vest.
プロテクターでした
Chapter 71: "Sparks"
Bra bra bra, my new braaa!
ブラブラブ～ラ わしの…
Anyway, look how excited she
is over a single present.
それにしてもプレゼント一つに
この喜びよう
She's only a child, but she came all the
way from England just to see Sister.
小さくてもステラは イギリスから
追って来る程シスターが好きなんだ…
If she finds out Sister is in love with Maria,
もしシスターが マリアさんの事を
好きだなんて知ったら…
This thing
she'll turn out just like that thing!
第二のアレが生まれるのは必至…！
Hey, Rec. Welcome.
やあ リク いらっしゃい
Ya goin' somewhere?
シスター どっかに行くんけ？
Just a quick visit to Maria's.
ああ ちょっとマリアの所に
なっ… シ シスター！
Sister!
'Kay, be safe!
そうけ
気をつけてな
Sure.
KITCHEN
ス… ステラ シスターの行き先
気にならないの？
Stella, aren't you curious
about where Sister was going?
He already told us, dummy.
To see the Virgin Mary.
さっき聞いたじゃろうが
マリア様の所じゃ
Virgin... Mary?
マリア… 様？
Jesus's mom! Whenever Sister has any leftover
cookies, he goes and donates them to her.
イエス様のお母さんじゃ
シスターはクッキーが多く出来た時は
マリア様に捧げに行くんじゃ！
Uhh...
ふーん…
Although, he's been a lot more
devoted to her lately,
でもそう言えば 最近いつも
マリア マリアと…
compared to how he was back in England.
イギリスにいた時より いっそう
信仰に磨きがかかっとるなあ…
But that name he said... I feel like
I've heard it around here before.
それにマリアって… よく考えると
他に聞いた事あるのう…？
そっ… そんな事ないよ！
Oh, I doubt that!
There are lots of people here I haven't met yet.
わし まだ話しとらん人
結構おってのう…
That's totally okay!
それでいいんじゃない？
Agreed! I don't care about anyone but Sister.
そうじゃな！
シスター以外どうでもいいわ
That's the spirit!
そうだよ！
あ… 危なかった…
That was close.
Sister has a crush on Maria,
from the farm nearby.
シスターは 牧場のマリアさんが
好きなんだよ…
H-Hoshi!
ほっ 星っ！
The lady from the farm? Her name's Maria?
牧場のお姉さん
“マリア” って言うんけ？
Bingo.
そうよ
お前 何ばらしてんだよ！
What the hell are you doing?!
So Sister's really been talking about...
じゃあシスターが…
いつも話しとるのは…
どああ ちっ 違う 違うっ
No, not at all!
How low can you get?
お前 酷すぎるぞ！ 何とかフォロー…
Help me out!
Hey, stupid.
バカやろう…
Better to lose all hope now
than later on down the line!
失恋するなら傷の浅いうちだろうがよ！
Eh?
You have no idea how painful
unrequited love can be.
てめえなんかに 片思いの辛さが
分かってたまるか…！
Unrequited love?
片思いの辛さ…？
But she's just a little girl.
でも まだ小さいのに…！
Stella...
ステラ…
New...
secret technique!
新奥義！
Ave Death Maria!
“アヴェ死 マリア”
Ave Death?!
あべしっ！
This is it. I'll destroy her.
ぬうぅぅ… これじゃ… これで決めたる
This shall be her downfall!
これでマリアを破る！
Downfall?!
破る！？
I guess I was just in the wrong
spot at the wrong time.
俺はただ技のかけやすい所に
居ただけのようです
Chapter 72: "MSB (Mad Sad Brothers)"
クッフッフッ… シスターに近づいた事
She'll regret ever deceiving Sister like this.
100回後悔さしたるでぇ…！
な… なは…
Wha?
Stella! You've heard the way
he talks about her, right?
ステラお前… シスターの
ノロケ聞いてたんだろ？
Sister's plain obsessed with Maria!
シスターはマリアに首ったけだ！
I'm fully aware.
分かっとるわい…
Then why?
じゃ 何で…
And what's with the growth spurt?!
てゆうか何 そのステラ その大きさ！？
ほにょ… ほにょ…
It's unrequited love, don't you see?
し 失恋だぞ！ 分かってんのか！？
No matter how much Sister might love Maria,
シスターがいくら
マリアの事が好きでも…
I love Sister a hundred times more!
わしはその100倍
シスターが大好きじゃあ！
ガガーン
I don't like that word, "unrequited."
大体日本語は変じゃあ！
Heartbreak? Sure, that's a word I understand. My heart's definitely shattered.
“ハートブレイク” は分かるわ
心が痛いのは仕方ないわい…
But what's this crap about "unrequited"?!
けど何が“失恋” じゃい！
Even if every speck of hope is gone,
I won't give up on my feelings!
１ミリの望みもなくたって…
この気持ちは失わんのじゃあ！
ア… アネキ！
Big Sis!
Now stand tall!
さあ 立つんじゃあ！
Before my world-ending attack, won't you...
反撃開始の前に わしの手料理の
taste my cooking?
味見をしてくれんかいのう？
Big Sis! Yes!
はいっ アネキ！
This is my special dish.
これが
わしの自信作…
Wow, looks delicious!
わあ～ おいしそう
Sautéed starfish!
ヒトデのソテーじゃ！
It's au naturel.
天然物じゃ
Hurry up and eat, while it's still hot.
あったかいうちに… の？
ばう… ばう…
The first supper of the brokenhearted tag team.
失恋タッグ 誕生の晩餐です
Chapter 73: "The Tyrant King"
Love is a powerful emotion.
“好き” という想いは強い
People sometimes gain miraculous
strength in the name of love.
人はその想いの強さにより 時に
思いもよらない力を発揮したりする
Boss, the time has come.
ボス 時間でございます
Good. I shall go forth,
うむ… 行くかの
for the sake of my love for Sister.
わしとシスターの愛のために
Yes, this is also...
そう これも…
The target is Maria! I will have her head!
目指すはマリア その首じゃあ！
Big Sis!
アネキィ！
You're the best, Boss!
最高っす ボスー！
The miraculous strength of love.
これも愛の奇跡
We just have to accept the fact that Stella has turned into a freak.
もうアレがステラなのは認めるとして…
Her head!
首じゃあー！
首ー！
Head!
Judgment day is upon her!
断罪じゃあー！
Judgment!
断罪ー！
ちょっ お前ら！
Hey, come on!
You guys are seriously taking this too far.
さっきから言うことが物騒すぎだぞ
After all, Maria's just a delicate, harmless woman—
まさかとは思うけど マリアさんは
か弱い女性なんだから…
人の心配よりも…
Before worrying about others,
don't you think you should worry about yourself?
自分の首の心配をした方が
いいんじゃないか？
You should probably get out
of your enemy's sight. Fast.
いつまで敵陣にいるつもりだ？
へっ…？ て 敵陣？
My enemy?
ギャアアアーー！
Ahh, and so then you came here to warn—
まあ それで私の所へ来てくれ…
Or maybe you just ran away?
というより 逃げ込んできたのね？
They were threatening to decapitate me!
だってあいつら “首” とか言いながら
追いかけてくるんですよ！
You need to get out of here!
マリアさんも逃げたほうがいいです！
Maybe you haven't noticed, but
Stella is actually incredibly violent!
マリアさんは知らないでしょうけど
ステラは普段ネコかぶってて
実は 超凶悪な子で…
うふふっ 嬉しいわ
This is perfect.
I like her cute version, but I've been
itching to meet the real Stella.
ネコかぶったステラちゃんも
かわいかったけど
素のあの子とも話をしてみたかったのよ
へ？ ネコかぶってるの知って…
So you knew?
With how noisy she is? Of course.
あれだけ騒いでれば 知ってるわよ
Hey, Maria. When's it gonna start?
おいマリア いつ始まるんだ？
What are we even waiting for?
出し物というのは何だ？
Just a little longer, my pets!
もうすぐよー 主賓の方々！
You invited them?
呼んだんですか！？
ははっ だって 面白そうじゃない？
Yup. Isn't this exciting?
What?! Hell no! You're in deep—
はあ！？ 面白くないですよ！
マリアさんの身が危な…
それは平気よ
I'll be just fine.
Because...
だって…
I just knew you'd come running and
volunteer to protect me with your life.
リク君が走って駆けつけて
体を張って守ってくれるって信じてたから
おあっ！
We challenge you!
たのもーう！
Please help me, Rec.
助けてねリク君 強がってるけど…
I might act tough, but I'm scared beyond belief.
私 本当は怖くって…
My legs are frozen in fear, so I'll
just sit over here and watch!
足がすくんで動けないけど
ここからずっと 見守ってるから
You're just perched up there
waiting to enjoy the show!
もんのすごく
高見の見物席じゃないですかー！
Oh, Rec! I figured you'd be holed
up at home, crapping yourself.
おう リク！ 部屋で
震えてるかと思ったぜ！
思ったぜー！
Crapping yourself!
I can't run away from these guys twice!
しかし こいつらから２回も逃げるのは…
Whoa, what? Nino?
ってあれ？ ニノ！？
Yo.
おう
And I definitely can't wimp
out in front of my girlfriend!
それに恋人の前で 弱気な俺を
見せる訳にはいかない！
It's fine. No matter how Stella looks
on the outside, she's still just a child.
大丈夫だ… 今は何故かこんなでも
中身は子供…
I'll use logic to shut her down.
大人の意見で 黙らせてやる
Now, now, Stella. I understand
that you're upset and confused.
なあー ステラ
いいかい 君は今混乱しているんだ
Your emotions are running wild, so you
don't realize what a mistake this is.
一時の感情に流されて
間違いをおかそうとしているんだよ
Perfect... she's sure to understand!
大丈夫… きっと分かり合える！
So let's just calm down, oka—
なっ！ だから落ち着いて…
YOU WILL GIVE ME YOUR HEAD RIGHT NOW!
オマエ クビ ヨコセ…
Maria... I'd rather face the Death Omen Star
than try to reason with her right now.
マリアさん
アレと話をするためには
“死兆星” を見る覚悟がいるみたいです
んはあ… まったく 頼りないわね
God, Rec. You're such a spineless crybaby.
リク君は
I can't help it! She has surpassed
human limits! She's a beast!
だって！ 人か獣かと問われたら
獣に近い感じですもん！
Fine, whatever.
まぁ いいわ
Stella, did you need something from me?
ステラちゃん
私に御用よね
OH YEEAAAAAAHH!!!
そうじゃあー!!
ちょっ シスター
二人を止めてあげて下さい！
Sister, you have to put a stop to this!
Don't be ridiculous. If I were to interfere now, Maria might...
バカを言うな
そんな事をしたらマリアに…
Now's no time to worry about what she'd say!
嫌われたくないとか言ってる場合では…
いや… そうじゃなく…
No, that's not what worries me.
Maria would kill me.
マリアに 殺される…
She'd kill me a hundred times over.
100回… 殺される…
I've developed a secret technique just for you.
わりゃあのために編み出した
新奥義の力
Feast your eyes on this!
今こそ見したるけん
Secret technique...
奥義
Ave Death—
“アヴェ死…”
Where did she go?
どこへ！？
No need to rush, Stella.
せっかちね ステラちゃん
Let's have a little chat first.
まず おしゃべりでもしましょうよ
No way! Big Sis gave up her back!
まさか アネキが
背後を取られるなんて…！
ああっ それだけじゃない！
And that's not all...
Look!
見て！
All of Maria's fluffy sheep...
さっきまでモコモコだった 羊達が…
They've been sheared clean!
きれいに剃毛されている…！
All that in a split second? Impossible!
まさかあの一瞬で！？
バカな…！？
おあ？
はっ さすがマリア
Maria never ceases to amaze.
It brings back memories...
初めて会った日を思い出すな
When we first met,
戦場ですれ違いざまに
she shaved my head nearly bald.
“波平カット” にされたあの日を
Her flawless movements...
隙のない動き…
It was love at first sight.
一目惚れだった…！
Um, excuse me!
あのー すみません
What happened just now?
何なんですか 今のマリアさんの動き
Was that another war story? You're not
just living out some fantasy, are you?
っていうか 戦場の思い出！？
それ シスターの妄想じゃなくて！？
あっ… まさか マリアさんも元軍人！？
Is Maria a former soldier, too?!
No, Maria worked for—
いや マリアは
某国の…
Actually... I forgot.
いや… いきなり忘れた
She silenced him!
口止めした！？
Do I have to give up?
わしは負けたのけ？
Until now, I... I...
今まで… ずっと ずっと…
いっ いやあーん！
シスターに好きになって貰えるように
I've been training so hard just so
Sister would fall in love with me!
一生懸命修行してきたのにー！
あ… ステラ…
Stella...
I'm such a weakling. I should just...
こんな弱いわしなんか… わしなんか…
Seppukuuu!
切腹じゃーい！
うをォォー！
SAMURAI！
Big Sis, calm down!
アネキ 落ち着いて！
Lemme go!
放さんかー！
You're not weak at all, Stella.
弱くなんかないわ ステラちゃんは
うはあっ！
Whaddya want, Maria?
Big Sis doesn't need your pity.
何だよマリア アネキは慰めなんか
好きな人の前で 自分の気持ちを
ありのまま出せるなんて
To be able to confess your feelings
in front of the person you love...
That's an amazing thing, Stella.
すごい事なのよ ステラちゃん
You're a very strong and beautiful young lady.
あなたは とっても強くて素敵な女の子
Do you think you and I could be friends?
お友達になれないかしら？ 私達
Not a chance in hell! You haven't
seen the last of Big Sis!
なれるわきゃねーだろ！
アネキは負けたわけじゃねーからな！
Don't worry, I'm gonna go medieval on—
大丈夫！ アネキの無念は 俺が…
Shooting Star!
“シューティングスター！”
メコーッ！
メェ～
Aww. Stella, that's a cute little move.
まあ ステラちゃん
かわいい技ね
I wouldn't mind showing you how to do it later.
じゃ じゃったらこんど教えたるけん！
メェ～
It was the birth of the cruelest,
most violent tag team ever.
最悪に凶悪なタッグの誕生でした
Chapter 74: "True Self"
My favorite magazine and cola.
好き～な雑誌とコーラ～
And a pack of Seven Star.
あと セブンスター
はい
Of course.
Every girl in the world...
世の女の子は～
That'll be 790 yen, please.
790円になります
Should have that one-length hair going on.
みんな
ワンレンにすればいい～
ねえ 今の人 かっこよくない？
That guy was really cute, huh?
Oh, yeah. I see him in here a lot.
そうそう あの人たまに来るのよ
Even if all the ladies of the world
had that one-length hair,
世界中の女の子が フンフンフフン…
Love
I'll—
I'll always love yours the best, dammit!
君のワンレンが一番好きだ
この野郎ー！
あー 気持ちいい天気だなあ…
What a beautiful morning.
It makes me glad to be alive.
何かこう 心がウキウキするよ
But it's kind of strange how normal this place is,
despite being just a little bit above the riverbank.
それにしても ちょっと上にあがっただけで
なんてまともな世界なんだろう
Crap! Someone's going down toward the river.
うわっ！ 一般の方が
河川敷に降りてるぞ
This is bad. He needs to get out of there ASAP!
まずいよ…
すぐ戻ってきた方が身のため…
Ah, dammit! That's Hoshi's trailer!
ダメだ！ それは星のトレーラー！
Hey, it's not abandoned!
ただの廃車だと思ったのか！？
あっ！ ちょっと 君！
Hey! Hey, you!
Don't go in there! That's someone's house!
ダメだよ！ そこ人が住んでるから！
えっ 早く！ 怖いものを見る前に
Hurry, before you're scarred for life!
Get ou—
出てっ…
What?
何
Um... no... I wasn't talking to you.
Didn't someone just... go inside?
あ… いや… お前じゃなく
誰か車に入って来たろ？
What? No. It's just me in here.
は？ ここには俺しかいねーよ
Huh? But I just—
はぁ！？ だって今っ
Oh my god. Did you... eat him?
まさかお前… 喰っちまったのか…？
That must be it. I can't think
of any other explanation.
そうだな…？
いや それ以外に考えられない
I've discovered your secret!
俺には今 はっきりと分かった！
Main Body
Real Mouth
Front View
Ornament
Side View
Main Body
Real Mouth
Ornament
Bottom View
Main Body
Real Mouth
Ornament
That "mask" of yours is really your body!
お前の本体が マスクだと言うことが！
Hi, there! Would you like to be my friend?
コンニチハ ボクト オトモダチニナッテ
Whoa, you're totally cute. Yeah, let's be friends!
わあー かわいい！
いいよ いいよ
You deceived the unsuspecting young
man with your fanciful appearance.
そのファンシーな姿で
妖精を装って青年に近づき…
Hey! What's up?
やあ 来ちゃったー！
You casually invited him into your trailer.
青年を無邪気に トレーラーに誘い込む
And then, when he wasn't looking...
そして油断したところを…
うひゃひゃひゃ…
You feed on the flesh of the living.
こんな風に 人の体の養分を
糧として生きる…
You're a parasitic life form!
寄生生物だったんだよ！
You're a freak!
こえーよ!!
Chapter 75: "The Brightest Star"
You flesh-eating starfish!
この人喰いヒトデめ！
God, just shut up already!
The "young man" you saw was me!
あー うるせえ うるせえっ！
ちげーよ さっきの青年が俺なの！
It was still early, and I wanted to
pop out to the store real quick.
早朝だし コンビニ行くだけだと思って…
チッ スッピンで出るんじゃなかったぜ…
Why'd I leave without my face on?
な… スッピンって…
Your face—
Wait, so if that guy I saw was really you,
じゃあまさか 本当に
さっきの青年がお前とすると…
then you admit that thing's just a mask?!
お前はそれを
“マスク” だって認めるのか？
Of course it's a friggin' mask.
“マスク” に決まってんだろ
I figured he was like the Chief,
pretending to be something non-human.
村長と同じで“人間じゃない” って
言い張るタイプかと…
Then why do you always wear
that thing around here?
じゃ何で橋の下で
いつもそんなもん被ってんだよ！
This is just my personal philosophy, but
これはさ 俺の持論なんだけどよ…
a masked man without a mask is just as
naked as a hot dame without her makeup.
マスクマンのスッピンと
ギャルのスッピンの重さは同じだと思うのよ
Why would I ever let someone like
you see me without my mask?
お前ごときに そんなスッピンを
くれてやる訳にはいかないね
I don't wanna hear about your
repressed feminine side!
知らねーよ！ そんな乙女心！
I just assumed the whole "mask" thing
was like your personal trademark.
俺はそのマスクが お前のポリシーだと
思ったから納得してたのに…
Well, of course it's my trademark, too!
もちろん
ポリシーよ！
You know what? I'm feeling good today. So I'm
gonna tell you the story behind the mask.
そうだな 今日は機嫌がいいから
特別にマスクの理由
教えてやってもいーぜ
Is this gonna be his origin story?
それはこいつの昔の話って事か？
It all began four years ago.
そう あれは４年前…
Luna-2 / Gravity
Rainy Day Service / Osaka
Ashen / Invitation
1 Ore no Ballad
2 Ore no Tank-top
3 Ore no Love Song
4 Ore no Message Song
5 Ore no Fickle Salad
6 Ore no Crib
7 Ore no Hip-Hop
8 Ore to Sama Dasashi
9 Ore no Bonus Track
Ore no 3rd Album
～ I made this ～
Ore no 3rd Album / Me
~I made this~
Bonjour Musume. / Seeds of Love
Spade / Body and Soul
Hirai Yawara / Hell
Flippers / GAMERA TALK
SMAC / The Only Snot in the World
Utatada Hikaru / tra
Me / Ore no 3rd Album
My third album had just reached
the top of the charts—
俺のサードアルバムが
オリコンで１位をとった頃の事よ
Huh? What do you mean, "top of the charts"?
ちょっと待て オリコンが何だって？
What's with that look of disappointment?
何だそのガッカリ顔！
I don't have time for your delusions.
俺 お前の妄想に
付き合う気はないんだけど
My story is totally non-fiction!
このお話は ノンフィクションです！
How could any of those ludicrous songs
of yours ever get that popular?!
お前のあのへんちくりんな歌で
デビューできる訳ないだろ！
Ludicr—
へんちくっ！
Heh. You're a sharp bastard, I'll give you that.
フッ 鋭いじゃねーか てめぇ…
He just straight-up admitted it. Was I too harsh?
ずいぶん大人しく認めたな…
言い過ぎたか？
You're exactly right. I have
no talent for writing music.
そうよ… 俺は作詞作曲の才能がねぇ…
But my producer was an
absolute marketing genius.
けど 俺のプロデューサーが
才能の塊みたいな男で…
I just sang whatever he told me to.
俺は言われるがままに歌っていた…
Ore n
o
3rd
Album
～ I made this ～
Me / Ore no 3rd Album
Utatada Hikaru / tra
SMAC / The Only Snot in the World
Flippers / GAMERA TALK
Hirai Yawara / Hell
Acting as if I'd had anything
to do with their creation...
表向きは 俺が全部やってる
みたいな顔でな
I was constantly frustrated and angry.
当時の俺は いつもイライラしてて
I would come down here
whenever I had some spare time.
休みが入る度に
一人でこの河川敷に来た
I'd play all the stuff my producer had rejected,
or songs I'd written to let off steam.
歌わせてもらえなかった自作の歌や
ストレスをぶつけただけの即興…
Hey, missy.
おい嬢ちゃん
You're wasting your time sitting
there listening to my shitty music.
俺の歌なんか聴いたって
面白くねーだろ！
That girl turned out to be my
goddess, ruler of my desti—
そう！
そこにいた少女こそ 俺の運命の女神！
Hey...
なぁ ちょっといいだろうか
Just a couple questions.
I'm just getting to the best part!
Chill the hell out, would ya?
何だよ 今すげーいい所だろうが！
空気読めよ！
First of all, why were you wearing a
freaking crescent-moon mask back then?!
その前に お前の頭が
満ち欠けしてんだよ！
ってゆうか 何でもう被ってんの！？
フッ 昔からロッカーには
自傷癖がある奴が多い！
Lots of rock stars have weird
habits they don't like to talk about.
In this case, my weird habit
was to wear a moon mask.
俺の場合は 月のマスクを
被る事だったのさ
Trying to pull off the "Sid Vicious Fantasy" look?
ファンシーな“シド・ヴィシャス” だな
Well, anyway...
まあ とにかくだ
The girl sitting there was Nino.
そこにいたのは ニノだった
I wanted to be alone, so I
just ignored her at first.
一人になりたかった俺は
初めずっと無視してたんだが
Worms are always sittin' there, chewin'
on dirt. Even though it's frickin' gross!
ミミズは土ばっかり食ってる～
おいしくないのに～
土！ 土！ 土！ 土！ 土～
Dirt!
Nino was always there, listening to my songs.
ニノはいつでも
俺の歌を聴いていてくれた
Hey, so... you got a name?
なぁお前 名前はあるのか？
Can't you tell by looking? I'm Moon.
見りゃ分かるだろ お月さんだよ！
Moon? Don't be silly. The Moon's way up there.
お月…？
バカ言うな 月はあそこにいるぞ
Be that as it may, I'm still Moon!
それでも 俺はお月さんなんだよ！
Okay, so why's that?
根拠はあるのか？
Because the moon's light is only a reflection
of the sun. And I'm the same way!
お月さんってのはなぁ…
太陽のお陰で光ってられる星よ
俺もだ！
My producer's the sun. I can't sing for
shit without him. I can't shine on my own.
プロデューサーって
太陽がいなけりゃ歌えねぇ
自分の力で光れねぇ
情けない衛星よ…！
I'm a pathetic satellite.
I knew you were lying. Just look at yourself.
ホラ見ろ やっぱり嘘じゃないか！
あぁん！？
Aren't you down here, singing all on your own?
お前 自分で歌ってるじゃないか
This stuff's a giant bag of crap
compared to the music I play up there!
こんなの 俺が仕事で歌ってる
歌に比べたら カスだ！
Well, I think they're awesome. You're not Moon.
私は好きだ
お前は 月じゃないな！
You're the brightest star in the sky!
お前はピカピカの一等星だろ！
Do I get a gold star?
図星だろ
She told me Venusians are masters
at distinguishing celestial bodies.
金星人は星を見分けるのがうまいのだと
彼女は教えてくれた
Don't tell me that's the reason
behind your ridiculous star mask!
だからって星型のマスクを被るなーーっ！
You sonuvabitch, that's all you have to say after such a heartwarming story?
てめぇ 今の美しい話の感想がそれかよ
Sorry, I just needed to get it out of my system.
You won't hear another peep out of me.
いや 一応言っときたかっただけ
これ以上のコメントは よしとくよ…
へっ ま いーか
It's all good, man. My luck-in-love
rating for today is maxed out!
今日の恋愛運マックスだしな！
But if what he just told me is true...
Could he really be a former celebrity?
しかし 今の話が本当なら
こいつ実はすごい奴なのか？
Hey, so... were you really that famous?
お前さ そんなに売れてたの？
Huh? Oh, yeah, for sure. But that's
all in the happy past, now.
ん？ おーよ
今となっては いい思い出だぜ
I shall investigate further.
ちょっと探りを入れてみるか…
おっほん
So you were on "Sure Thing," then?
“いいとも” 出た？
Yup, I sure was. Man, now that was a fun show.
あー 出た出た
なつかしーな～
Lennon-san
Congrats!
Will you come on the show tomorrow?
アシタキテクレルカナー？
Sure thing!
いいともー！
My very good friend,
John, invited me to come on.
マブダチのジョンから
電話をもらってな…
And I called Elvis to ask him to be the next guest.
次の俺の回には
エルヴィスに電話したっけ
Sure thing!
イイトモー！
He screamed it so loud, his damn voice cracked!
叫ぶから声割れちゃっててさー
フッ ヘヘヘッ
Honestly, he's just an
overenthusiastic old fart to me.
俺に言わせりゃ あいつなんて
ただの元気のいいおっさん！
Wow, that's just amazing. Was it some kind
of bring-back-the-dead prime time special?
へー すげぇ
それってさぁ…
“降霊会スペシャル” か何か？
Nope. Elvis even revealed his
mailing address on the air.
いやー エルヴィスなんか
生放送中に自宅の住所をさぁ
They're both definitely dead, right?
みんな“故人” だよね…
ハハハハ フヘヘ アハハ…
So the whole thing is a delusion, after all.
やっぱり妄想かもしれません
Chapter 76: "Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge"
Huh? What's the deal with the bed?
It's Nino's turn this time, but she was
fast asleep when I went to get her.
So I just shoved her in along with the bed.
あの日夕暮れ
What if she rolls off into the water?!
Nino, I'll save you!
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
I never knew REM sleep could be so
acrobatic. Nino's quite remarkable.
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
I've been teaching Nino some self-defense
moves while she's asleep. I call it sleep-aikido.
Wow. A very impressive skit.
もう行かなくちゃ
Agreed. It's been a real success.
Her signature move is "The—"
この空泣き出す前に
"Kappa Dokkin Kappadokia!"
"Miracle Mute Metamorphosis!"
Yeah, that's what I meant to say.
サカサマになって
Sister, how do you say this?
君の事探して
S-
And this?
-te-
This one?
-lla.
いつまでも僕らは
And this one?!
I love...
Time's up, Stella.
たどり着けないまま
Next time, on 10 BRIDGE!
Diplomacy is futile against brute force.
橋の下に立って
流れる渦に在って
Illustration: Yukiko Sumiyoshi
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
あれ？ お立ち台じゃねーの？
今回はニノの番だったんですが
すっかり寝てしまいまして
仕方なくベッドごと…
って もし落ちたら
危ないじゃないですか！
ニノさん！ 今行きまーす！
おあっ！？
うおぁぁー!!
ぐぉぉ…
相変わらず アクロバットな
寝相の悪さだな ニノの奴
いや あれは私が眠ってるニノだけに
仕込んでおいた 合気道ですよ
へー じゃあ立派な一発芸だな
ええ 一発芸です
題して “ザ…
－ギラファノコギリクワガタ”
-マンディプラリスフタマタクワガタ”
あ やっぱそっち？ そっちぃ？
シスターこれなんて読むの？
これは？
じゃあ これは？
愛し…
ステラ時間だ
次回　「10 BRIDGE」
チッ… やはり交渉よりも
武力行使じゃのう